Guide to the Kiwanis Club of Houston records, 1919-2017 MS 619
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Kiwanis Club of Houston records
1919-2017
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Kiwanis Club of Houston
MS 619
72.25 Linear Feet (70 boxes)
This collection comprises records of the Kiwanis Club of Houston's board of directors, committees, projects, finances, conventions, and retired members, as well as records from the Kiwanis Foundation of Houston, the Kiwanis Texas-Oklahoma District, and Kiwanis International.
Organizational History History
Founded in 1919, The Kiwanis Club of Houston is the oldest Kiwanis Club chapter in the Houston area. The Club is a part of Kiwanis International, a community service organization with a network of over 15,000 Kiwanis clubs across the globe. The Kiwanis mission statement is "to serve the children of the world." With over 100 members, the Houston Club serves the children and young people of the Houston area.
The Houston Clubs major initiatives include the Key Clubs, which organize high school students to participate in community service projects, and raising funds through its Annual Charity Golf Tournament and Bike Ride. The Club also run the Kiwanis Back to School Express, and serves free meals at Bo's Place. In 1966, the Houston Club created the Kiwanis Foundation of Houston to assist in raising funds and supporting the Club's services.
Scope and Content
This collection comprises records of the Kiwanis Club of Houston's board of directors, committees, projects, finances, conventions, and retired members, as well as records from the Kiwanis Foundation of Houston, the Kiwanis Texas-Oklahoma District, and Kiwanis International. It includes audio recordings, DVD, Beta, and VHS recordings, nearly 1000 photographs, and ephemera such as posters, banners, flags, and awards. The collection reflects the history of the club from its founding in 1919 into the 21st century.
Series I: Board of Directors
Series II: Committees
Series III: Projects and Fund Raisers
Series IV: Club Finances
Series V: Awards
Series VI: Conventions
Series VII: Bulletins
Series VIII: Retired and Deceased Members
Series IX: Foundation
Series X: Texas-Oklahoma District
Series XI: Kiwanis International
Series XII: Correspondence
Series XIII: Legal Documents
Series XIV: Ephemera
Series XV: Photographs
Series XVI: Audio Cassettes
Series XVII: Videos and DVDs
Series XVIII: Awards
Series XIX: Kiwanis Club Administration
Series XX: Financial records
Series XXI: Membership
Series XXII: Events
Series XXIII: Grants
Series XXIV: Kiwanis International
Series XXV: Memorabilia
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Access restrictions
Collection open for research without restrictions, except for the Club Finances series and the Foundation Finances subseries.
Acquisitions information
Donated by the Kiwanis Club of Houston on April 3, 2014
Index Terms
Subjects
Voluntarism; Social life and customs
Document Types
letters (correspondence); scrapbooks; minutes (administrative records); photographs; awards; audiotapes; videotapes
Subjects (Corporations)
Kiwanis International; Kiwanis International. Texas-Oklahoma District; Kiwanis Club of Houston; American Freedom Train Foundation
- Series I: Board of Directors, 181968; 0 Linear Feet
  - Presidential Papers, 181969; 0 Linear Feet
    - Presidential Papers, 1950s-1980s; 181970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Papers, 1990-1996; 181971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Presidential Papers (1 of 2), 1997-2000; 181972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Presidential Papers (2 of 2), 1997-2000; 181973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Presidential Papers, 2000-2006; 181974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - President Curtis Johnson, 1978-1979; 181981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - President Eugene Shepherd, 1979-1980; 181982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - President Keys Curry, 1980-1981; 181983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - President Eric Lundien, 1981-1982; 181984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - President Robert Rowan, 1982-1983; 181985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - President Marvin Cluett, 1983-1984; 181987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - President William J. Miller, 1984-1985; 181988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - President Carlos Leach, Jr., 1985-1986; 181989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - President George Donnelly (1 of 2), 1986-1987; 181990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - President George Donnelly (2 of 2), 1986-1987; 181991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - President Kelly Frels (1 of 2), 1987-1988; 181992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - President Kelly Frels(2 of 2), 1987-1988; 181994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - President John K. Ewing, 1988-1989; 181995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - President William Dwyer(1 of 2), 1989-1990; 181996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - President William Dwyer (2 of 2), 1989-1990; 181997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - President Dwight Beach, Jr., 1990-1991; 181998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - President Rock N. Houston (1 of 2), 1991-1992; 181999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - President Rock N. Houston (1 of 2), 1991-1992; 182000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - President Corky Fowler, 1992-1993; 182002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - President Carlos Hamilton, Jr., 1993-1994; 182003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - President Fielding Cocke (1 of 2), 1994-1995; 182004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - President Fielding Cocke (2 of 2), 1994-1995; 182005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - President Milton McGinty, 1995-1996; 182006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - President Jerry Metcalf, 1996-1997; 182007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - President Glenn Johnson(1 of 2), 1997-1998; 182008 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - President Glenn Johnson (2 of 2), 1997-1998; 182009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - President Alan Kaniss, 1998-1999; 182011 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - President Jack McGinty, 1999-2000; 182012 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - President Betsy Griffin, 2000-2001; 182013 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - President Bob Shultz (1 of 2), 2001-2002; 182014 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - President Bob Shultz (2 of 2), 2001-2002; 182015 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - President Bob Mahan, 2002-2003; 182016 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - President Bill Sherwood, 2003-2004; 182017 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - President Carlos Bujosa, 182018 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - President Mark Brooker, 2005-2006; 182019 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - President Gabrielle Merrill, 2006-2006; 182020 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - President Richard Tholstrup, 2006-2007; 182022 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Board Materials, 182024
    - Board Materials, 1994-1997; 182025 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Board Materials, 1999-2002; 182026 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Board Materials, 2002-2005; 182027 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Board Materials, 2005-2007; 182029 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Proposal for Membership- Original, 182030 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 182032
    - Meeting Minutes- Directors, 1926-1927; 182034 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1928-1929; 182035 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1930-1932; 182036 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1933; 182037 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1934; 182038 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1935; 182039 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1936; 182040 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1937; 182041 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1938; 182042 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1939; 182043 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1940; 182044 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1941; 182045 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1942; 182046 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1943; 182047 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1944; 182048 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1945; 182049 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1946; 182050 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1947; 182051 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1948; 182052 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1949; 182053 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1950; 182054 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1951; 182055 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1952; 182056 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1953; 182057 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1954; 182058 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1955; 182059 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1956; 182060 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1957; 182061 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1958; 182062 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1959; 182063 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1960; 182064 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1961; 182065 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1962; 182066 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1963; 182067 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1964; 182068 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1965; 182069 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1966; 182070 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1967; 182071 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1968; 182072 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1969-1970; 182073 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1970-1971; 182074 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1972; 182075 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1973; 182076 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1967-1973; 182077 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1973-1974; 182078 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1976-1977; 182079 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
    - Meeting Minutes- Board, 1977-1978; 182081 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Notes, 182082
    - Organizational Meeting, 8/30/2007; 182084 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Meetings, 2007-2008; 182085 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meetings, 2007-2010; 182086 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Organizational and President's Reports, 1950-1996; 181975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Secretaries Council, 182083
    - Administrative Secretaries Council, 182087 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Series II: Committees, 182088
  - Committee Organization, 182089
    - Committee Chairmen, 1954-1975; 182090 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Committee Letters, 182091 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Manual for Club Presidents, "Responsibility", 1963; 182092 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Rosters: Houston Committees, 182093 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Committee Rosters, 1950s; 182094 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Committee Rosters, 1960s; 182095 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Committee Rosters, 1970s; 182096 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Committee Rosters, 1980s; 182097 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Committee Rosters, 1990s; 182098 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Committee Volunteers, 2003-2004; 182099 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Boys and Girls Committee, 182100
    - Houston Preparatory Academy, 182102 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Career Guidance Committee, 182101
    - Career Guidance File, 182103 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Education Committee, 182104
    - Education File, 182105 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Education Seminars, 182107 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Kiwanis Education, 2001-2002; 182108 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Goodwill and Visitation Committee, 182109
    - Goodwill and Visitation File, 182110 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Memorials, 182111 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - House Committee, 182112
    - House Committee, 182119 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Introductory Material for new Office, 182120 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - R.M. Crowe (other), 182121 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Verisign, 2005; 182122 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - International Relations Committee, 182113
    - International Relations File, 182123 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Inter-club Relations Committee, 182114
    - Inter-club Relations File, 182124 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - London Inter-club, 1979-1980; 182125 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 182115
    - Long Range Planning, 182126 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Every Member Attitude Survey, 4/20/1989; 182127 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Major Emphasis Committee, 182116
    - Major Emphasis File, 182128 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Membership Committee, 182117
    - Membership File, 182129 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Membership Statistical Records, 182130 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Membership, 1980s; 182131 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Membership, 2000-2001; 182132 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Membership, 2004-2005; 182133 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Membership, 2007-2009; 182134 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1925; 182135 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1930; 182136 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1940; 182137 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1950s; 182138 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1960s; 182139 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1970s; 182140 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1980s; 182141 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Directories: Houston Membership, 1990s; 182142 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Directories: Houston Membership Bylaws, 182143 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Area Club Memberships + Directories, 182144 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Membership Roster, 2003-2004; 182145 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Attendance Reports, 1970s-1990s; 182146 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Attendance and Membership Reports, 1980s; 182147 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Attendance Reports, 1982-1983; 182148 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Activity and membership Reports, 1990s; 182149 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Attendance, 2001-2002; 182150 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Attendance, 2002-2003; 182151 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Attendance, 2004-2005; 182152 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Perfect Attendance Report, 2001-2002; 182153 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Senior Membership, 182154 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Membership- Senior Status, 2004-2005; 182155 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Membership- Senior Status, 2005; 182156 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Membership- Senior Status, 2007; 182157 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Membership- Senior Status, 2010; 182158 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Membership- Distinguished Status, 182159 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Life Member Status, 182160 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Honorary Membership, 182161 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Membership Orientation, 182162 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Members' Affiliations, 182163 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Membership Drive, 182164 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Annual Club Mtg. Perfect Attendance, 2003-2004; 182165 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - ACE Workshop, 2010; 182166 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - CHIP Clique Seminar, 182167 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Greater Houston Partnership, 182168 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Greater Houston Partnership, 1997; 182169 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Military Affairs Committee, 182118
    - Military Affairs Files, 182170 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Music Committee, 182171
    - Music File, 182176 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Song books and sheet music, 182177 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Notification Committee, 182172
    - Notification File, 182178 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Office Committee, 182173
    - Office File, 182179 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Programs Committee, 182175
    - Programs- History, 182181 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Programs, 1950s-1970s; 182182 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Programs, 1980s-1990s; 182183 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Programs- Major General John Singlaud File, 182184 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Programs- General Haig, 182185 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Programs- Key Curry, Mike Molsey, 2002-2003; 182186 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Program- Habitat for Humanity, 182187 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Costa Rican President's visit, 12/13/2001; 182188 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Speaker Information, 2002; 182189 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Speakers/ Programs, 2004-2005; 182190 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Programs/ Speakers, 2006; 182191 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Speakers, 2006; 182192 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Public and Business Affairs Committee, 182174
    - Public and Business Affairs Files, 182180 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Public Relations Committee, 182193
    - Public Relations File, 182199 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Reception and Fellowship Committee, 182194
    - Reception and Fellowship File, 182200 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Spiritual Aims Committee, 182195
    - Spiritual Aims File, 182201 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Sponsored Youth Committee, 182196
    - Sponsored Youth File (1 of 1), 182202 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Sponsored Youth File (2 of 2), 182203 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Know to say No! to Drugs, 182204 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Kids Triathlon Registrations, 1997, 182205 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Kids Triathlon File, 1997, 182206 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Circle K Clubs (1 of 2), 182207 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Circle K Clubs (2 of 2), 182208 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Key Clubs (1 of 5), 182209 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Key Clubs (2 of 5), 182210 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Key Clubs (3 of 5), 182211 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Key Clubs (4 of 5), 182212 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Key Clubs (5 of 5), 182213 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Monthly Club Activity Report, 182214 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Builders Club, 182215 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Kiwanianne Club Program, 182216 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Fire Fighter's Club, 182217 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Social Committee, 182197
    - Social File, 1985-1986; 182218 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Social File, 1994-1995; 182219 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Social File, 1995-1996; 182220 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Social File, 1996-1998; 182221 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Social File, 2004-2005; 182222 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Social File, 2008-2009; 182223 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Holiday Gatherings, 182224 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Florence Travel Pack, 182225 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Christmas Cocktail Buffets, 182226 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Holiday, 2006; 182227 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Party Guest Book, 182228 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Ladies Day, 182229 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Theater under the Stars, 182230 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - President's Ball, 182231 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Barbecues, 182232 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Picnics, 182233 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Rick Figueroa Ranch Picnic, 4/2003; 182234 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Special Guest Day, 182235 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Gilbert + Sullivan Society, 182236 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Leadership Dinner, 182237 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 50th Anniversary, 1969; 182238 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 50th Anniversary, 1969; 182239 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 60th Anniversary (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Kiwanis Club of Orilla Inc. Anniversary, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Golf Tournaments, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Wild Game Dinner, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Tea Dance, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Rodeo Party, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Valentine Dinner-Dance, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Cocktail Party for Gray'ce Callahan, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Hunting and Fishing Survey (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Tennis, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Roger Moore-UNICEF campaign, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Shriner B.A.S.H. Bike Ride, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Golf Tournament, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Baseball Games, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Tennis, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Bike Ride, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - British Isles Tour Cancelled, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 31-32)
    - South America Trip, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Vienna Trip, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Danube Adventure, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 35-39)
    - Bluebonnet Tour, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Tacos and Telescopes, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Browning Plantation, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Bush Presidential Library Tour, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Fort Hood Trips, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 44-45)
    - Alaska Cruise, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Jingle Bell Express, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Series III: Projects and Fund Raisers, 182198
  - Iodine Deficiency Disorder Elimination Project, 183497
    - Project: Iodine Deficiency Disorder Elimination, 182240 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - IDD Campaign, 1999-2000; 182241 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - IDD Campaign Summaries, 182242 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Hoby Foundation, 183498
    - Hoby Foundation, 182243 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Hoby, 2000; 182244 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Hoby Foundation, 2001-2002; 182245 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Hoby, 2002; 182246 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Hoby, 2004; 182247 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Post Cancer Patient Assistance Network, 183501
    - Post Cancer Patient Assistance Network Proposal, 182248 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Project Apple, 183502
    - Project Apple, 182249 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - GLADD Program, 183503
    - GLADD Program, 182250 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Gumball Project, 183504
    - Gumball Project, 182251 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Project GRAD, 183505
    - Project GRAD, 1999; 182252 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Glaucoma Screening, 183506
    - Glaucoma Screening, 1974-1975; 182253 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Points of Light Program, 183507
    - Points of Light Program, 182254 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Cans Festival Project, 183508
    - Project: Food Bank, Cans Festival, 182255 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Beans and Rice Project, 183509
    - Beans and Rice Project, 182256 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Texas Children's Hospital Sickle Cell Anemia Project, 183510
    - Texas Children's Hospital Sickle Cell Anemia Project, 2000; 182257 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Adolescent Maternity Project, 183511
    - Adolescent Maternity Project, 182258 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Project: New Directions
    - New Directions, Inc., 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Project: Renaissance Singers, 183512
    - Project: Renaissance Singers, 1975-1978; 182259 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Project: Military Air Safety and Traffic Service
    - Military Air Safety and Traffic Service, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - American Freedom Train, 183513
    - American Freedom Train Visit Finances, 182262 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - American Freedom Train Account Ledgers, 182263 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - American Freedom Train Assorted Records and Correspondence (1 of 3), 182264 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - American Freedom Train Assorted Records and Correspondence (2 of 3), 182265 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - American Freedom Train Assorted Records and Correspondence (3 of 3), 182266 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - American Freedom Train VHS tape, 182267 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - American Freedom Train Photos, 182268 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - American Freedom Train, "Kiwanis in Action" Scrapbook Photos, 182269 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - American Freedom Train Scrapbook Photos, 182270 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - American Freedom Train Scrapbook Decoration, 182271 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - American Freedom Train Scrapbook Pages, 182272 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - American Freedom Train Scrapbook Pages, 182273 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - American Freedom Train Ledgers, 182274 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - American Freedom Train Certificate of Appreciation to Kiwanis Club, 182275 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - American Freedom Train: "Kiwanis in Action- American Freedom Train Project" Scrapbook, 1975-1976; 182276 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - American Freedom Train: American Freedom Train print, 182277 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Herman Eye Center, 183561
    - Project: Herman Eye Center file, 1975-1999; 182278 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Families under Urban and Social Attack, Inc., 183562
    - Families under Urban and Social Attack, Inc. file, 182279 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Houston Ear Research Foundation, 183577
    - Houston Ear Research Foundation file, 182280 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - JROTC, 183578
    - JROTC- Houston Independent School District file, 182281 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Project: Florence Crittenden Home, 183579
    - Project: Florence Crittenden Home file, 1968-1973; 182282 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Project: Boys Harbor, 183584
    - Project: Boys Harbor file, 1978; 182283 (Box 13, Folder 9)